(this.webpackJsonpquizerr=this.webpackJsonpquizerr||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,,,function(e,i,a){e.exports=a(15)},,,,,function(e,i,a){},function(e,i,a){},function(e,i,a){},function(e,i,a){"use strict";a.r(i);var t=a(0),n=a.n(t),s=a(6),o=a.n(s),r=(a(12),a(1)),h=a(2),u=a(4),l=a(3),d=(a(13),function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var i=Object(l.a)(a);function a(){var e;return Object(r.a)(this,a),(e=i.call(this)).state={anime:[{name:"Naruto",value:"naruto"},{name:"Attack on Titan",value:"aot"},{name:"My Hero Academia",value:"mha"},{name:"Parasyte The Maxim",value:"ptm"}]},e}return Object(h.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-2 m-5"},n.a.createElement("h2",null,"Select a Topic")),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},this.state.anime.map((function(i){var a=i.name,t=i.value;return n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-success p-2 m-2 bwidth col-sm-9 col-md-6 col-lg-6",onClick:function(){return e.props.changeTopic(a,t)},key:t},a)}))))}}]),a}(t.Component)),c=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var i=Object(l.a)(a);function a(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,a),(t=i.call(this,e)).state={question:t.props.question,options:t.shuffleArray(t.props.options),answer:t.props.answer,qpoints:1,buttonClass:"btn btn-info m-2"},t}return Object(h.a)(a,[{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(e){for(var i=e.length-1;i>0;i--){var a=Math.floor(Math.random()*(i+1)),t=e[i];e[i]=e[a],e[a]=t}return e}},{key:"correct",value:function(e){var i=[e.value],a="btn btn-info m-2",t=this.state.qpoints;e.value===this.state.answer?(a="btn btn-success m-2",this.props.score(t,t)):(a="btn btn-danger m-2",this.props.score(0,t)),this.setState({options:i,buttonClass:a,qpoints:0}),this.props.setSolutions(this.state.question,e.value,this.state.answer)}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-4 m-2"},n.a.createElement("h2",null,this.state.question),this.state.options.map((function(i){return n.a.createElement("button",{className:e.state.buttonClass,onClick:function(){return e.correct({value:i})},key:i},i)}))))}}]),a}(t.Component),m=[{question:"What is alterego of Nine Tails Fox",options:["Red Demon Fox","Kurama","Shukaku","Matatabi"],answer:"Kurama",id:521},{question:"Whom did Naruto kiss first?",options:["Sasuke Uchiha","Hinata Hyuga","Fuka","Sakura Haruno"],answer:"Sasuke Uchiha",id:522},{question:"With whose fight did Naruto first use Nine tails Chakra?",options:["Sasuke","Neji","Haku","Gaara"],answer:"Haku",id:523},{question:"Who tricked Naruto into stealing a sacred scroll?",options:["Iruka","Mizuki","Sasuke","Zabuza"],answer:"Mizuki",id:524},{question:"What is another word for ninja?",options:["Genjutsu","Shinobi","Arigato","Chakra"],answer:"Shinobi",id:525},{question:"Which of the legendary sannin becomes the fifth Hokage?",options:["Jiraya","Tsunade","Orochimaru","Kakashi"],answer:"Tsunade",id:526},{question:"Who was the first ninja Sasuke Uchiha copied with the Sharingan?",options:["Rock Lee","Itachi Uchiha","Orochimaru","Naruto"],answer:"Rock Lee",id:527},{question:"Which famous clan was completely massacred?",options:["Uchiha","Hyuuga","Uzamaki","Nara"],answer:"Uchiha",id:528},{question:"What piece of jewelry do the Akatsuki wear?",options:["Earrings","Nose rings","Rings","Anklets"],answer:"Rings",id:529},{question:"What is the village where Naruto lives called?",options:["Sunagakure","Kyuubigakure","Uzamagakure","Konohagakure"],answer:"Konohagakure",id:530},{question:"How many ninja from Konoha went on to the third stage(after the preliminairies) of the Chunin Exams?",options:["Six","Five","Seven","Four"],answer:"Five",id:551},{question:"What's the name of the leader of the toads?",options:["Wise Frog Master","Giant Toad King","Master Froggo","Great Toad Sage"],answer:"Great Toad Sage",id:552},{question:"How did Hidan (one of the Akatsuki member) die?",options:["He can't die","He was starved","He was trapped in Shadow Posession Jutsu while Ino and Choji killed him","His own god betrayed him"],answer:"He can't die",id:553},{question:"Who gave their life to save Gaara?",options:["Kankuro","Sasori","Chiyo","Fugi"],answer:"Chiyo",id:554},{question:"Who created the Akatsuki?",options:["Orochimaru","Tobi","Itachi","Yahiko"],answer:"Yahiko",id:555},{question:"What is Minato's nickname?",options:["The Yellow Flash","The Red Flash","Flash Ninja","Flash of the Leaf"],answer:"The Yellow Flash",id:556},{question:"Which member joined team Taka/Hebi first?",options:["Karin","Jugo","Suigetsu","They all joined at the same time"],answer:"Suigetsu",id:557},{question:"What is Kakashi/Obito's Sharingan ability?",options:["Tsukuyomi","Amaterasu","Kotoamatsukami","Kamui"],answer:"Kamui",id:558},{question:"What was Zabuza's nickname?",options:["The demon of the hidden mist","The silent killer","The demonic killer","The monster of the mist"],answer:"The demon of the hidden mist",id:559},{question:"What is Tsunade's addiction?",options:["Men","Gambling","Work","Alcohol"],answer:"Gambling",id:560},{question:"What is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",options:["Lotus of Destruction","Shadow Lotus","Primary Lotus","Fiery Lotus"],answer:"Primary Lotus",id:581},{question:"What does ANBU mean?",options:["Special Unit Forces and Recruits","Special Assassination and Tactical Squad","Undercover Ninjas: Black Operations","Hidden Agendas of Shinobi and Allied Tactics"],answer:"Special Assassination and Tactical Squad",id:582},{question:"How did Sakumo Hatake (Kakashi's father) die?",options:["He got killed on a mission","He was killed by Madara","He naturally died of old age","He committed suicide"],answer:"He committed suicide",id:583},{question:"Who were the first reincarnates of Indra and Ashura?",options:["Naruto and Sasuke","Madara and Hashirama","Sasuke and Itachi","Kakashi and Guy"],answer:"Madara and Hashirama",id:584},{question:"Who was the youngest Jonin?",options:["Kakashi","Itachi","Neji","Sakura"],answer:"Kakashi",id:585},{question:"What does Gaara's tattoo mean?",options:["Orphan","Monster","Love","Hate"],answer:"Love",id:586},{question:"What is Sasuke's team called?",options:["Tiki","Taka","Toka","Toku"],answer:"Taka",id:587},{question:"Which of these characters has Kurama's chakra?",options:["Menma","Guren","Sora","Haku"],answer:"Sora",id:588},{question:"Which of them is not a Kekkei Genkai?",options:["Particle style","Byakugan","Sharingan","Tenseigan"],answer:"Particle style",id:589},{question:"Who is not part of the Team Kurenai?",options:["Shino","Kiba","Hinata","Neji"],answer:"Neji",id:590}],p=[{question:"What is Family name of Levi?",options:["Ackerman","Akermaan","Ackarmon","Ackermen"],answer:"Ackerman",id:421},{question:"Along with Eren, who was shot and tranquilized in the back of a wagon?",options:["Mikasa","Historia","Shasha","Armin"],answer:"Historia",id:422},{question:"Who was the only half family member to visit Historia on the farm?",options:["Uri","Drick","Florian","Frieda"],answer:"Frieda",id:423},{question:"Who is the shortest soilder of 104th cadet",options:["Eren","Mikasa","Armin","Historia"],answer:"Historia",id:424},{question:"What is name of the civil war within the empire?",options:["War of Giants","Great Titan War","Black eldien","Great Eldien War"],answer:"Great Titan War",id:425},{question:"Who is responsible for maintaining order within the internment zones such as Liberio?",options:["Survey corps","Marley police","Marley public security","KingsGuard"],answer:"Marley public security",id:426},{question:"Eren gained Hardening after consuming a bottle labelled?",options:["Hardening","Confidential","Deflection","Armor"],answer:"Armor",id:427},{question:"What is Eren's Titan Form called?",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:428},{question:"Who is the slowest Titan",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Colossal Titan",id:429},{question:"Which Titan has the hardest skin?",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Armored Titan",id:430},{question:"Armin confiscated what from Marlo and Hitch?",options:["Food","Supplies","Rifles","Info"],answer:"Rifles",id:451},{question:"What is Symbol of Eldiens",options:["White Band","Tattoos","Shorts","Gears"],answer:"White Band",id:452},{question:"Who saved Hange from Cart titan",options:["Jean","Eren","Mikasa","Armin"],answer:"Jean",id:453},{question:"Who saved Mikasa from the Titans",options:["Attack Titan","Female titan","Armored Titan","Armin"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:454},{question:"Who is commander of survey corps?",options:["Erwin","levi","Armin","Mikasa"],answer:"Erwin",id:455},{question:"Who almost killed the Beast Titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Levi",id:456},{question:"Who became the new Colossal Titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Armin",id:457},{question:"Who became the new Jaw Titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Ymir","Armin"],answer:"Ymir",id:458},{question:"Who is Scientist researching on Titans?",options:["Hange","Ymir","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Hange",id:459},{question:"Who stopped Annie escape from the fight with Eren?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Mikasa",id:460},{question:"What is the name of island in Attack on Titan?",options:["Ellis island","Paradis island","Funen island","Elldian island"],answer:"Paradis island",id:481},{question:"Who of the 104th Cadet Corps has been referred to as \u201cGoddess\u201d?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Historia","Armin"],answer:"Historia",id:482},{question:"Which character has their ears turn red when they lie?",options:["Mikasa","Eren","Historia","Armin"],answer:"Eren",id:483},{question:"How many Titan Shifters are there in AOT?",options:["Six","Ten","Nine","Eight"],answer:"Nine",id:484},{question:"Which Titan Shifter can maintain their titan form only for short period ?",options:["Attack","Armored","Colossal","Jaw"],answer:"Colossal",id:485},{question:"Who saved Armin from Titan's mouth?",options:["Mikasa","Eren","Historia","Levi"],answer:"Eren",id:486},{question:"What is Annie\u2019s last name?",options:["Reiss","Lonarld","Leonhart","Tierce"],answer:"Leonhart",id:487},{question:"What is life span pf Titan shifters",options:["9 years","15 years","13 years","12 years"],answer:"13 years",id:488},{question:"Which Titan did Ymir eat to return to her human form?",options:["Attack","Armored","Colossal","Jaw"],answer:"Jaw",id:489},{question:"Which gear is used in fight of reteak maria",options:["Anti personnal uni-directional","3D manuer gear","Breach Cannons","Anti personnal omni-directional"],answer:"Anti personnal omni-directional",id:490}],w=[{question:"Izuku Midoriya is also known as:",options:["All Might","Endeavor","Deku","Stendhal"],answer:"Deku",id:621},{question:"What is a \u201cquirk\u201d?",options:["a hero","a superpower","a battle","an event"],answer:"a superpower",id:622},{question:"How did Izuku Midoriya got his powers?",options:["Eats hair","Trains really hard","Five hour energy","Tons of steroids"],answer:"Eats hair",id:623},{question:"Who is Number one hero?",options:["Midnight","Cementross","No. 13","All Might"],answer:"All Might",id:624},{question:"What is the opposite of One for All?",options:["None for All","All for One","Anti power","One in All"],answer:"All for One",id:625},{question:"What is All Might's quirk called?",options:["One For All","All For One","Super punchy power","One Strong Boi"],answer:"One For All",id:626},{question:"Who does All Might, the world's greatest hero, pass his powers to? ",options:["Tenya","Kashuki","Izuku","Tsugu"],answer:"Izuku",id:627},{question:"What school does Izuku dream of having powers and attending as a child?",options:["UD High","UA High","UC High","UB High"],answer:"UA High",id:628},{question:"What is Aizawa's hero name?",options:["Eraser Head","Reset Head","Restarted","Disabler Head"],answer:"Eraser Head",id:629},{question:"What does Izuku call his childhood friend as?",options:["Bakugo","Katsuki","Baku","Kacchan"],answer:"Kacchan",id:630},{question:"What is All Might\u2019s real name?",options:["Enji Todoroki","Chizome Akaguro","Toshinori Yagi","Ochaco Uraraka"],answer:"Toshinori Yagi",id:651},{question:"What is Endeavor's original name?",options:["Shinji Nishiya","Enji Todoroki","Sorahiko","Sir Nighteye"],answer:"Enji Todoroki",id:652},{question:"Who is the class president of Class-A? ",options:["Tenya ilda","Bakugo","Todiroki","Midoriya"],answer:"Tenya ilda",id:653},{question:"Who is Class-A teacher?",options:["midnight","Aizawa","nezu","All Might"],answer:"Aizawa",id:654},{question:"Which characters hero name is Uravity?",options:["Uraraka Ochaco","Izuku Mydoria","Tenya ilda","Todiroki shouto"],answer:"Uraraka Ochaco",id:655},{question:"What quirk does Kasuki Bakugo have?",options:["One for all","Dark Shadow","Erasing","Explosion"],answer:"Explosion",id:656},{question:"Who runs the Infirmary at UA high?",options:["Hiroshi Shinso","Mashirao Ojiro","Recovery Girl","Fumikage Tokoyami"],answer:"Recovery Girl",id:657},{question:"What is Shigaraki Tomura quirk?",options:["Strength","Teleportation","Hands","Disintegration"],answer:"Disintegration",id:658},{question:"What punch does All Might use to defeat All For One?",options:["American Smash","Global Smash","Ultimate Smash","United States Of Smash"],answer:"United States Of Smash",id:659},{question:"How many students are in class-A?",options:["19","18","20","21"],answer:"20",id:660},{question:"Which successor of One For All is Izuku Midoriya?",options:["7th","8th","9th","10th"],answer:"9th",id:681},{question:"Who is the rubber like villain that All Might fought at the training camp?",options:["Nezu","Nomu","Tomura Shigaraki","Kurogiri"],answer:"Kurogiri",id:682},{question:"What was hero killer stain's Quirk ability?",options:["Freezing people using their blood","Blades strikes to draw blood","Make others scared","Casting a scary image in opponent"],answer:"Freezing people using their blood",id:683},{question:"What did the doctor say was responsible for Izuku not getting his quirk?",options:["Two joints on his pinky toe","A hole in his heart","An injury on his leg","A fractured elbow"],answer:"Two joints on his pinky toe",id:684},{question:"What job did All Might initially suggest to Izuku since he wanted to save people?",options:["A Soldier","A Policeman","A Doctor","An Ambulance Driver"],answer:"A Policeman",id:685},{question:"Where does Izuku train, in order to be able to receive All Might's power?",options:["Dogobah Municipal Memorial Park","Dogobah Municipal Football Stadium","Dogobah Municipal Play Park","Dogobah Municipal Beach Park"],answer:"Dogobah Municipal Beach Park",id:686},{question:"For how long does Izuku train to inherit All Might's quirk?",options:["2 Years","10 Months","6 Months","1 week"],answer:"10 Months",id:687},{question:"Which of these superheroes is Tenya's brother?",options:["Kurogiri","Tamura","Nomu","Ingenium"],answer:"Ingenium",id:688},{question:"What does Izuku Midoriya's nickname Deku mean?",options:["World's Greatest Hero","Chimp","It means nothing","One who can't Achieve/do Anything"],answer:"One who can't Achieve/do Anything",id:689},{question:"What's the name of the group within the League Of Villains that Dabi leads?",options:["Vanguard Attack Squad","Vanguard Action Squad","Frontier Action Squad","Frontier Attack Squad"],answer:"Vanguard Action Squad",id:690}],k=[{question:"How did Shinchi accidently get Migi in his right hand?",options:["Parasyte landed in Shinchi's right hand","Shinchi squashed it with his right hand","Parasyte was in Shinchi's meal and then entered right arm","Parasyte entered right arm but then Shinchi blocked it with his headphones"],answer:"Parasyte entered right arm but then Shinchi blocked it with his headphones",id:721},{question:"What happened when Shinchi's parents went on vacation?",options:["His mother was killed in a car accident and his father managed to survive","His father was killed in a car accident his mother managed to survive","His mother was taken over by a parasyte and his father managed to escape","His father was taken over by a parasyte and his mother managed to escape"],answer:"His mother was taken over by a parasyte and his father managed to escape",id:722},{question:"How did Ryouko Tamiya die?",options:["Killed by another parasyte","Killed by Shinchi","Killed by humans","She didn't die"],answer:"Killed by humans",id:723},{question:"What's Shinchi's last name?",options:["Izumi","Uragami","Nagai","Uda"],answer:"Izumi",id:724},{question:"What did Shinchi call his parasyte?",options:["Ryouko","Migi","Miki","Gotou"],answer:"Migi",id:725},{question:"Who is Shinchi's best friend and love interest?",options:["Yuko","Kana","Akiho","Satomi"],answer:"Satomi",id:726},{question:"Who is this main character?",options:["Migi","Shining isamu","Ryouko Tamiya","Shinichi Izumi"],answer:"Shinichi Izumi",id:727},{question:"Which parasyte has a human baby?",options:["Ryouko Tamiya","Miki","Hideo Shimada","Kusano"],answer:"Ryouko Tamiya",id:728},{question:"What is the first parasyte Migi killed?",options:["Flying Dog parasyte","Mr A parasyte","The one that attacked school","Shinchi's mom"],answer:"Flying Dog parasyte",id:729},{question:"Who is Kazuyaki?",options:["Shinchi's girlfriend","Shinchi's dad","Shinchi's mom","Shinchi's friend"],answer:"Shinchi's dad",id:730},{question:"Why did Gotou wanted to kill Migi?",options:["He hated him","He thinks Migi is dangerous","To get Migi's host","To get Ryouko's attention"],answer:"He thinks Migi is dangerous",id:751},{question:"What was Ryouko goal to join Shinichi's school?",options:["To study about parasytes","To kill the students","To destroy the school","To kill Shinichi"],answer:"To study about parasytes",id:752},{question:"Which part of Shinichi's body did Migi join to?",options:["Left hand","Chin","Right hand","Chest"],answer:"Right hand",id:753},{question:"Who was the criminal that differentiated humans and parasytes?",options:["Tachikawa","Suzuki","Kimishima","Uragami"],answer:"Uragami",id:754},{question:"To whom does parasyte attach at lower jaw?",options:["Shiro Kuramori","Mamoru Uda","Makiko Hayase","Takeshi Hirokawa"],answer:"Mamoru Uda",id:755},{question:"What is the Mamoru's parasyte name?",options:["Joe","Joey","Jaw","Jack"],answer:"Joe",id:756},{question:"Where is Uda's parasyte present?",options:["Right hand","Head","Chin","Left hand"],answer:"Chin",id:757},{question:"After saving Shinichi's life, what was Migi sleeping time?",options:["3 hours a day","4 hours a day","5 hours a day","6 hours a day"],answer:"4 hours a day",id:758},{question:"What was the weapon Shinichi used to injury Mr.A?",options:["Knife","Chair","Desk leg","Stone"],answer:"Desk leg",id:759},{question:"Who was the investigator hired by Ryouko?",options:["Shiro Kuramori","Hirama","Takeshi Hirokawa","Yamagishi"],answer:"Shiro Kuramori",id:760},{question:"How many additional parasytes are present in Gotou?",options:["5","4","3","7"],answer:"4",id:781},{question:"Which parasyte has power to control 3 parasytes in Gotou?",options:["Migi","Joe","Miki","Kusano"],answer:"Miki",id:782},{question:"What human part is first taken over by parasyte?",options:["Brain","Neck","Right hand","Chest"],answer:"Brain",id:783},{question:"What is the special about Kana Kimishima?",options:["Ability to sense her lover","Ability to sense good people","Ability to change anyone","Ability to sense Parasytes"],answer:"Ability to sense Parasytes",id:784},{question:"Which hospital was Shinichi's dad hospitalised during his vacation?",options:["Shizuoka Hospital","Namiki Hospital","Sakurazaki Hospital","Izu Hospital"],answer:"Sakurazaki Hospital",id:785},{question:"What is not Migi's power?",options:["Conjure Blades","Detaching from Host","Control other parasytes","Amplifying hsot abilities"],answer:"Control other parasytes",id:786},{question:"When does Shinichi cries first time after being taken by Migi?",options:["Seeing a dead dog","His mother dies","During the death of Kana","After receiving Ryouko's baby"],answer:"After receiving Ryouko's baby",id:787},{question:"How does Shinichi's mother burn her forearm?",options:["Saving Shinichi from hot pot","Setting up a camp fire","While roasting sweet potato","During a fire accident"],answer:"Saving Shinichi from hot pot",id:788},{question:"When does parasytes show up?",options:["Day time","Night time","Evening","Sunrise"],answer:"Night time",id:789},{question:"Which parasyte is alive at the end of the show?",options:["Miki","Kusano","Gotou","Joe"],answer:"Joe",id:790}];function g(e,i){for(var a=[],t=0;t<i;t++)a.push(t);return(a=function(e){for(var i=e.length-1;i>0;i--){var a=Math.floor(Math.random()*(i+1)),t=e[i];e[i]=e[a],e[a]=t}return e}(a)).splice(0,e)}var f=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var i=Object(l.a)(a);function a(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,a),(t=i.call(this,e)).state={question:t.props.question,choosen:t.props.choosen,correctAns:t.props.correctAns,corClass:"p-2 m-2 corClass",wrgClass:"p-2 m-2 wrgClass"},t}return Object(h.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12 col-lg-12 p-2 m-2"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:this.state.choosen===this.state.correctAns?this.state.corClass:this.state.wrgClass},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-2"},n.a.createElement("b",null,this.state.question)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-2"},n.a.createElement("b",null,"Choosen Option : "),this.state.choosen),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-2"},n.a.createElement("b",null,"Correct Answer : "),this.state.correctAns))))}}]),a}(t.Component),y=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var i=Object(l.a)(a);function a(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,a),(t=i.call(this,e)).showSol=function(){t.setState({showSolu:!0})},t.state={score:t.props.score,title:t.props.title,noQuestions:t.props.noQuestions,solutions:t.props.solutions,showSolu:!1},t}return Object(h.a)(a,[{key:"comment",value:function(){var e=(100*this.state.score/this.state.noQuestions).toFixed();return e>=80?"You are a "+this.state.title+" master":e>=40?"You have to brush up your knowledge about "+this.state.title:"You may have to watch "+this.state.title}},{key:"render",value:function(){return n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-2 m-2"},n.a.createElement("h3",null,"Your Score")),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-2 m-2"},n.a.createElement("h2",null,n.a.createElement("strong",null,this.state.score,"/",this.state.noQuestions))),n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("h3",null,"Percentage : ",(100*this.state.score/this.state.noQuestions).toFixed(),"%"),n.a.createElement("br",null),this.comment()),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-warning p-2 m-4 text-white",onClick:this.showSol},"View Solution"),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary p-2 m-4",onClick:this.props.retake},"Retake Quiz")),n.a.createElement("div",null,this.state.showSolu?this.state.solutions.map((function(e){var i=e.question,a=e.choosen,t=e.correctAns;return n.a.createElement(f,{key:i+t,question:i,choosen:a,correctAns:t})})):null))}}]),a}(t.Component),q=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var i=Object(l.a)(a);function a(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,a),t=i.call(this,e),console.log("Main constructor running"),t.state={questions:[],points:0,noQuestions:6,topic:"naruto",title:"anime",responses:-1,solutions:[]},t}return Object(h.a)(a,[{key:"refresher",value:function(){this.setState({points:0,responses:0,solutions:[]})}},{key:"retake",value:function(){this.setState({points:0,responses:-1,solutions:[]})}},{key:"score",value:function(e,i){this.setState({points:this.state.points+e,responses:this.state.responses+i})}},{key:"changeTopic",value:function(e,i){var a=function(e,i){var a=[];if("naruto"===e)for(var t=g(i,m.length),n=0;n<i;n++)a.push(m[t[n]]);else if("aot"===e){var s=g(i,p.length);for(n=0;n<i;n++)a.push(p[s[n]])}else if("mha"===e){var o=g(i,w.length);for(n=0;n<i;n++)a.push(w[o[n]])}else if("ptm"===e){var r=g(i,k.length);for(n=0;n<i;n++)a.push(k[r[n]])}return a}(i,this.state.noQuestions);this.setState({topic:i,title:e,questions:a}),this.refresher()}},{key:"setSolutions",value:function(e,i,a){var t=this.state.solutions;t.push({question:e,choosen:i,correctAns:a}),this.setState({solutions:t})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("div",null,this.state.responses<0?n.a.createElement(d,{changeTopic:function(i,a){return e.changeTopic(i,a)}}):null),n.a.createElement("div",null,this.state.responses>=0?n.a.createElement("h2",{className:"p-2 m-5"},n.a.createElement("strong",null,this.state.title," Quiz")):null),n.a.createElement("div",null,this.state.responses>=0&&this.state.responses<this.state.noQuestions?this.state.questions.map((function(i){var a=i.question,t=i.options,s=i.answer,o=i.id;return n.a.createElement(c,{question:a,options:t,answer:s,key:o,score:function(i,a){return e.score(i,a)},setSolutions:function(i,a,t){return e.setSolutions(i,a,t)}})})):null),n.a.createElement("div",null,this.state.responses===this.state.noQuestions?n.a.createElement(y,{score:this.state.points,noQuestions:this.state.noQuestions,retake:function(){return e.retake()},title:this.state.title,solutions:this.state.solutions}):null))}}]),a}(t.Component),v=(a(14),function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var i=Object(l.a)(a);function a(){return Object(r.a)(this,a),i.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(h.a)(a,[{key:"darkMode",value:function(){document.body.classList.toggle("darkMode")}},{key:"render",value:function(){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header p-2"},n.a.createElement("h1",{className:"quizHead"},"ANIME QUIZERR"),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle custom-control custom-switch"},n.a.createElement("input",{type:"checkbox",className:"custom-control-input",id:"darkSwitch",onClick:this.darkMode}),n.a.createElement("label",{class:"custom-control-label",for:"darkSwitch"},"Dark Theme"))),n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement(q,null)))}}]),a}(n.a.Component));Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));o.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(v,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}],[[7,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.d82c6871.chunk.js.map